myhoneybakedstore.com 2018-05-01

# Privacy Policy | HoneyBaked Ham

We recognize and respect the privacy and the security of your personal information. We value your trust in our company and will only use your information as we have described in this Security and Privacy Policy. 

**Safe Online Shopping**  
We want you to feel completely secure when ordering from our Website. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), and digital certificate technology, which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information, protects its integrity, and allows it to be properly identified in Internet based transactions. Your information is protected by the password assigned to you. Protect the confidentiality of that password and do not disclose it to third parties. Contact our Customer Service by email if you would like further information on Website security. 

**1\. What Personal Information We Collect**

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide when you register as a user of honeybakedonline.com (or affiliated Web sites including honeybakedham.com). This information includes: your email address and the password you create when you register. You can browse our online store without registering, but you must register to purchase or take advantage of promotions or special Website features. We may also confirm personal information when you contact our Customer Service by email or telephone. This allows us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity. We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to honeybakedonline.com (or affiliated Web sites including www.honeybakedham.com).

Collected information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type, and the address of a referring Website, if any. We collect this information to improve the quality of your visit to our site. We do not currently sell or rent your email address information to any third parties that are not directly affiliated with the HoneyBaked Ham Company of Georgia. When you visit honeybakedonline.com (or affiliated sites), you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) which is stored on your computer's hard drive, if you select either the "remember my name" or "remember my name and password" option. The cookie identifies you when you visit so we can optimize and customize your online shopping experience. If you choose not to use cookies, you may not have access to certain features of our site such as "remembering" your password, storing your shopping cart for later use and, in the future, providing a more personalized shopping service. Your browser (according to that particular browser's instructions) can also be configured to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. 

**2\. Purchasing Our Products & Registering with HoneyBaked Ham**

When you purchase by credit card, we collect your name, billing address, card type, number, and expiration date so that we can bill you for your purchase. We also collect information for shipping your order, including the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient.

When you become a registered user of our site, you can choose to save your billing information and shipping information as part of "your account". You can view or change your account information at any time by logging in with your email address and password. You can also change your address by emailing our Customer Service. When you register with our site, you may elect to receive information from us (by U.S. Mail or email) on product updates, promotions and discounts, and other company information. 

**3\. How We Use Your Personal Information**

On a limited basis, we may exchange or rent your mailing address with other approved catalog companies. Also, under special circumstances, such as when we believe that disclosure is required by law, we may disclose your personal information. Other than as stated above, we will share your information only with our own agents, representatives, and trusted service providers and contractors for limited purposes relating to this Website and the processing of your order. We may aggregate your information, without identifying you personally, to obtain statistical and demographic background on our customers. To prevent your name from being exchanged with other catalogers, please send your name, phone number and full mailing address to [ catalogservice@hbham.com](mailto:catalogservice@hbham.com). You can also be removed from our mailing list by emailing the above address. To opt-out of any of our email programs, simply click on the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of every email or contact us at phone numbers below. 

HoneyBaked Ham Customer Care: [1 800 367 7720](tel:800-367-7720)  
California Residents – [1 800 854 5995](tel:800-854-5995)
